to answer a question both are okay
options this option is called software
TLB miss handling and it has the
advantage of letting the operating
system use any sort of page table that
it wants because the hardware doesn't
really need to access the page table the
hardware simply has the TLB and the job
of the operating system is to put the
correct translations into the TLB but if
you use any organization for the page
table it wants so the operating system
for example may not even have the page
table in form of a table it can use a
binary tree or a hash table or anything
else it wants the second option where
the processor automatically reads page
tables and updates it will be is called
hardware TLB miss handling in this case
the page tables need to be in a form
that is easily accessible by the
hardware so we will have a flat or a
multi-level page table like we have seen
already in our previous videos this
approach does require more Hardware
because the hardware now needs to
actually be able to access the page
tables and sequence the accesses to the
multiple levels and so on but it is
faster than software handling this is
treated kind of like a cache miss almost
whereas here we need to execute a little
program to fill the TLB so because this
is faster and because hardware is cheap
these days most high performance
processors like x86 will use this
approach of hardware TLB miss handling
but some embedded processors will use
the software TLB miss handling because
they are concerned about the hardware
cost so they want to be as simple as
possible and also because in these
embedded processors TLB misses occur
less frequently because they are running
more regular applications